{
    "id": "359a989c42c548bc885da5816f38e013",
    "title": "Sentence conversion exercise",
    "exercises": [
        {
            "id": "6205e9eed1f54aeb9009ae59c3da13ec",
            "title": "Simple Or Complex",
            "questions": [
                {
                    "question": "He sold the house that belonged to his father.",
                    "description": "",
                    "answers": [
                        "Simple",
                        "Complex"
                    ],
                    "correct": 1
                },
                {
                    "question": "I have no money that I can lend you.",
                    "description": "",
                    "answers": [
                        "Simple",
                        "Complex"
                    ],
                    "correct": 1
                },
                {
                    "question": "The marks that were left by the whip are still visible.",
                    "description": "",
                    "answers": [
                        "Simple",
                        "Complex"
                    ],
                    "correct": 1
                },
                {
                    "question": "He prospered by the money he inherited from his father.",
                    "description": "",
                    "answers": [
                        "Simple",
                        "Complex"
                    ],
                    "correct": 1
                },
                {
                    "question": "A man who is dead has no worries.",
                    "description": "",
                    "answers": [
                        "Simple",
                        "Complex"
                    ],
                    "correct": 1
                },
                {
                    "question": "He sold his father’s house.",
                    "description": "",
                    "answers": [
                        "Simple",
                        "Complex"
                    ],
                    "correct": 0
                },
                {
                    "question": "I have no money to lend you.",
                    "description": "",
                    "answers": [
                        "Simple",
                        "Complex"
                    ],
                    "correct": 0
                },
                {
                    "question": "The marks left by the whip are still visible.",
                    "description": "",
                    "answers": [
                        "Simple",
                        "Complex"
                    ],
                    "correct": 0
                },
                {
                    "question": "He prospered by his father’s money.",
                    "description": "",
                    "answers": [
                        "Simple",
                        "Complex"
                    ],
                    "correct": 0
                },
                {
                    "question": "A dead man has no worries.",
                    "description": "",
                    "answers": [
                        "Simple",
                        "Complex"
                    ],
                    "correct": 0
                }
            ]
        }
    ]
}